A Guide to the WRVA Radio Collection, 1925-2000
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Photographs 1925-2000 (Box Boxes 33-66 and Negative Boxes 1-14)
  - Subseries C: Negatives (Box 1-10)
    - "Operation Flood" - U.S. Marine Reserve Trucks (I-III), Mar. 14-1963, 3 sleeves (Box 7)
    - "Operation Flood" - Lions Club Collections (Box 7)
    - Ortho Products Window Display, July 6, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Overstreet and Admiral recording rebuttal to Communist Party Secretary talk at UVA, Apr. 12, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Display in WRVA Theatre Lobby, Apr. 9, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Hand Cream Display in standard drug store, Mar. 1959 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Hand Cream Window Display - Hotel Richmond Snack Bar, Feb. 23-Mar. 2, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Lobby Display, Apr. 1, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Lotion Window Display, Feb. 26, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Samples at New Dominion Barn Dance, Jan. 24, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Silk 'n Satin on Theatre Marquee, Mar. 17, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Silk and Satin Window Display, Mar. 21, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Store Display at Ukrop's Supermarket, 1915 Mechanicsville Pike, during "Lewis Martin Week", Feb. 19, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Pacquin's Window Display, Apr. 3, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Carl Padow's Hams on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Dec. 10, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Parker Field - Yankees vs. Virginians, Apr. 15, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Carol Pavey Promotion, June 19, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Pearce, Oscar (Box 7)
    - Pearl's Laundry Quiz, Sept. 29, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Pepsi-Cola Window Display, Apr. 5, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Pepsi-Cola on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Apr. 13, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Griffin, Woodward Indoctrination Trip - Breakfast Studio "A", June 12, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Griffin, Woodward Indoctrination Trip - Tour of Larus & Brother Co., Inc. Plant, June 12, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Griffin, Woodward Indoctrination Trip - Lunch at Country Club of Virginia, June 12, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Griffin, Woodward Indoctrination Trip - Group Shot, June 12-13, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Griffin, Woodward Indoctrination Trip - Station Presentation, Colonial Room, Hotel Richmond, June 13, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Griffin, Woodward Indoctrination Trip - Williamsburg, June 13, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Performers (unidentified) (Box 7)
    - PGA Gold Tournament (Box 7)
    - Harold Phillips in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Harold Phillips - Dick Tisdale at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 20, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Playgoer's Guild Series (1-3), 3 sleeves (Box 7)
    - Preston, William R. (Box 7)
    - Bill Preston - John Tansey Staff Meeting (Preston explains pulse trends in 1957), Dec. 18, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Prestone Anti-Freeze Window Display, Nov. 10, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Prestone Anti-Freeze Window Display, Nov. 13, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Prestone Anti-Freeze on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Oct. 26, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Prestone Window Display - Hotel Richmond Snack Bar, Nov. 6, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Puritron Display - Miller & Rhoads, Apr. 15, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Purolator Dealers, Apr. 1961 (Box 7)
    - Purolator Filters with Miss Marcia Robbins, Nov. 28, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Queen Elizabeth - Patrick Henry Airport with Governor Stanley, Nov. 16, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Queen Elizabeth at Wren Building, William & Mary, Nov. 16, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Question Mark (?) - WRVA event, cold weather, lunch and speeches (1-7), 7 sleeves (Box 7)
    - R. W. Raabe in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 8)
    - R. W. Raabe - ID (head and shoulders), Mar. 3, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Rudy Raabe - staff meeting, Dec. 18, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Ralston-Purina on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Sept. 20, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Ray-O-Vac Batteries Lobby Display, Dec. 6, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Ray-O-Vac Batteries Window Display, Dec. 5, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Ray-O-Vac Window Display in Hotel Richmond snack bar, Oct. 11, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Ray-O-Vac Batteries on WRVA Theatre Display, Dec. 7, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Reaves, Archie (Box 8)
    - Reception for CBS Executives at Commonwealth Club (1-2), 2 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Reddi-Wip on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Jan. 4, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Red Heart Dog Food - Wood's Market, Aug. 21, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Reed, William T., Jr. (1-2), 2 sleeves (Box 8)
    - W. T. Reed, Jr., received W.R. Bishop Plaque from Delegate Tom Frost with John Tansey, Russell Carneal, and Brooks George, Jan. 31, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Sherwood Reeder, Richmond City Manager, with Richard Foster and Stirling King (Box 8)
    - Repine, Burt (Box 8)
    - R.J. Reynolds window display - Winston & Salem cigarettes, Feb. 2, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Rebecca Richardson (Miss Virginia 1956), Aug. 24, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Thomas H. Richardson, International League President with Mrs. Calvin C. Erma and Mrs. Gerry Waring, Feb. 15, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Richfood Coffee window display, Feb. 2, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Richmond Chamber of Commerce Outing - Frog Jumping Contest (1-2), June 14, 1962, 2 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Richmond Food Stores Display - Grand Opening of Warehouse, June 6, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Richmond-Petersburg Toll Road Opening, June 30, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Richmond TV Hearing in Washington (Box 8)
    - Richmond Tire & Rubber Company on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Jan. 26, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Richmond "Virginians" Bumper Strips on Red Top Cabs, Oct. 12, 1962 (Box 8)
    - Brick Rider ID shot, Feb. 7, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Brick Rider with Indian Princess, June 19, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Brick Rider Making TV spots, Oct. 16, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Phil Ruzzuto - CBS Radio Sportscaster, Apr. 11, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Miss Marcia Robbins - WRVA Radio Publicity Shots, Nov. 28, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Robinson, Lynn (Box 8)
    - Safeway Stores on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Apr. 17, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Carl J. Sanders (Box 8)
    - Santa Claus of WRVA on microphone (Box 8)
    - Scholarship Quiz (1-4), 1952, 4 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Scholarship Quiz (1-3), 1953?, 3 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Scholarship Quiz, 1953 (Box 8)
    - Scholarship Quiz - Highland Springs High School, Apr. 15, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Scholarship Quiz winners - William Roberts (James Blair High School, Williamsburg), Richmond Crinkley (Blackstone High School), and James Jarrell (Spotsylvania High School), May 15, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Lowell W. Scwab, Dr. William L. Curry and "Candy Twins", Lavona and Lavelda Rowe, Dec. 21, 1962 (Box 8)
    - Dr. Lowell W. Scwab, Dr. William L. Curry, Edith Price, Joy Smith, Betty Bulifant, and "Candy Twins", Lavona and Lavelda Rowe, Dec. 21, 1962 (Box 8)
    - Zachary Scott (Box 8)
    - Cecil Sheets (Box 8)
    - Shell News and Weather on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Aug. 8, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Sheltering Arms Hospital Drive, Nov. 14, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Ken Shelton with microphone and records, Mar. 30, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Ken Shelton with copy and microphone, Mar. 30, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Shoney's and Big Boy Restaurants - crowd shots and waitresses with Lyle Bradley (I-III), Oct. 30, 1962, 3 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Silver Dust - Lobby Display, Apr. 5 - May 3, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Silver Dust - Window Display, Apr. 5 - May 3, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Silver Star Quartet (1-2), 2 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Silver Star Quartet, May 1963 (Box 8)
    - Silver Star Quartet at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 20, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Silver Star Quartet at 1959 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 26, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith - 1957 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 27, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith - 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith with 1960 winners of WRVA trophy (sports), Earl Stoudt, University of Richmond half-back, and Ronald Gassert, UVA tackle, Dec. 14, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith head shots, Mar. 12, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith with Frank Messer, Dec. 13, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith and Frank Messer with "Vees" and "Yankees" players, Mel Roach, "Bullet Bob" Turley, Bill Stafford, and Eddy Casko, Feb. 15, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith and Frank Messer with Jerry Waring, Feb. 15, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith and Frank Messer with Jack White, Feb. 15, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith with Frank Messer, Jack White, General Manager of the New York Yankees, and Tommy Richardson, President of the International League, Feb. 15, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith - "The New Dominion Barn Dance", Dec. 7, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith and Tommy Richardson, President of the International League, Feb. 15, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith with Phil Rizzuto, Apr. 11, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith - "Sporting News" presentation with Harry Simkins, Clarence Brown, Chester Fritz, and Rex Collins, Jan. 28, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith in Thalhimer's Window with engineer Ed Hines, May 19, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith on "Virginians Caravan" at Gordonsville, Virginia, Apr. 12, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Bob Smith - WRVA-Radio Sports Awards for 1957 Season with Bobby Jordan (VMI) and Jim Kiser (UVA), Dec. 11, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Solarine Floor Wax Lobby Display, June 6, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Solarine Floor War Window Display, May 29, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Solarine Floor War at Wood's Market, May 29, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Solarine Floor Wax on WRVA Theatre Marquee (Box 8)
    - Southlanders Quartet (Box 8)
    - Cecil Spicer (Box 8)
    - S.S.S. Tonic window display in Standard Drug Store, Mar.-Apr. 1959 (Box 8)
    - S.S.S. Tonic window display at Hotel Richmond snack bar, Mar. 2-9 and Apr. 6-27, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Staff Members - Groups (1-3), 3 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Staff Shots of head and shoulders for Virginia State Police Press Pass, Apr. 1956 (Box 8)
    - Stanley, Thomas B. - Governor of Virginia (Box 8)
    - Governor Stanley before joint houses (Box 8)
    - Stassen, Harold with George Passage (Box 8)
    - 1957 State Fair Product Table, Sept. 27, 1957 (Box 8)
    - 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 8)
    - 1959 State Fair of Virginia (personality shots, product display booth, crowd shots, and Aaroe and products) (I-IV), Sept. 24 - Oct. 3, 1939, 4 sleeves (Box 8)
    - 1960 State Fair of Virginia (crowd shots at Mobile Studio, shots of Marcia Robbins Watts giving out shopping bags, farm products display booth) (I-III), Sept. 21 - Oct. 1, 1960, 3 sleeves (Box 8)
    - 1961 State Fair of Virginia (crowd shots, trailer shots, farm products display booth) (I-III), Sept. 21-30, 1961, 3 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 8)
    - Jack Stone (Box 8)
    - Jack Stone's Boat (Box 8)
    - Lewis E. Straus, Secretary of U.S. Department of Commerce, at John Marshall Hotel for Jaycees "Bosses' Night Dinner", Jan. 20, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz (I-II), 2 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz - 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz at Alcoa "Care Free Home" with Westhampton Junior Woman's Club, Dec. 10, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz Billboard on U.S. Route 250 West, June 20, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz Billboards, Nov. 10, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz - Crippled Children's Hospital, Dec. 30, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz - Easter Bonnet Contest Winners, Apr. 3, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz - Easter Bonnet Contest Winners (rejects), Apr. 3, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz at H-Fi Show at Hotel John Marshall, Sept. 21, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz with Hi-Fi Stereo Fair Poster at Hotel John Marshall, Sept. 14, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz with Interwoven Socks in Greentree's Window, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz with Edith Lindeman (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz at Arthur Murray Dancing Party, Tantilla Gardens (1-2), Jan. 28, 1958, 2 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz on microphone, Aug. 16, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz in Thalhimer's Window with engineer Mike Garthright, May 22, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Carl Stutz with Van Heusen shirt in Greentree's Window, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Sunshine Sue (1-3), 3 sleeves (Box 8)
    - Sunshine Sue - Good Luck Margarine (Box 8)
    - Sunshine Sue's Home (Box 8)
    - Sunshine Sue (photograph by Hugh Morton) (Box 8)
    - Super Suds at Wood's Market, Aug. 21, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Lillian Sutphin (Box 8)
    - Hardy J. Snyder (Box 8)
    - Taft, Senator Robert A. (Box 9)
    - "Tall Tales Contest" Winner, Bill Rothenberg, with Sandy and Lee Wicker, Aug. 5, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner - 1963 Home Show at the Arena with John Martin, Mar. 28, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner - AVIS Rent a Car Remote (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner - Brick Laying Contest (Southern Brick and Supply Co.), Apr. 28, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner - full length photo for Shoney's Display, May 23, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner with life-sized cutout of himself, July 1963 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner in Miller and Rhoads, 6th and Grace Streets Window, Oct. 10, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner in Mobile Studio at Arena, Oct. 22, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner in Mobile Studio at Miller and Rhoads May Sale at 5th and Grace Street, Apr. 26, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner at N.F. Jacobs Remote, Nov. 26, 1962 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey - Receiving Veterans Administration Award from Mr. Powell of Virginia Office, Apr. 3, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner interviews nurse during Sheltering Arms Hospital Drive, Nov. 14, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner in trailer at State Fair, Sept. 25, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner doing TV spot, May 15, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Ken Tanner at Virginia Stationery Company with Brooks George, Lou Dean, and Broaddus Jones, Oct. 24, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Tansey, John (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with 1962 Football Trophy Winners and Frank Messer, Dec. 12, 1962 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with Ballentine and Richmond "Virginians" personnel (Ed Phillip, Leonard Faupell, and Jerry Waving), Nov. 22, 1960 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with Walter W. Craigie and Dr. Lewis Webster Jones, president, National Conference of Christians and Jews (WRVA gets first annual Brotherhood Award for Crippled Children's Hospital Drive), Feb. 19, 1959 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with John S. Lanahan, president, and Charles M. Adams, sales manager, Richmond Hotels, Inc., June 1962 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with C.T. Lucy at retirement of Lucy, Oct. 2, 1961 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with H. Preston Peters, C.T. Lucy, and W.T. Reed, Oct. 2, 1961 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey at staff meeting, Dec. 18, 1957 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey at Lt. Governor A.E.S. Stephens - National Safety Council Award, May 5, 1960 (Box 9)
    - John Tansey with WRVA Trophy Football Winners, Don Christman and Earl Stoudt, Dec. 14, 1961 (Box 9)
    - "Telar" Anti-Freeze window display, Dec. 5, 1960 (Box 9)
    - "Telar" Anti-Freeze on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Nov. 14, 1960 (Box 9)
    - William D. Terrell, winner "Oldest Radio Contest", with Sue Patterson and Lee Wicker, May 28, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Sanford Terry (Box 9)
    - Tetley Tea, July 21, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Tetley Tea - Evans Supermarket, Glenwood Farms, Mar. 24-29, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Tetley Tea - Evans Supermarket, Jan. 1959 (Box 9)
    - Tetley Tea - Safeway Stores, Oct. 1958 (Box 9)
    - Texaco Window Display - Hotel Richmond Snack Bar, May 31, 1959 (Box 9)
    - William B. Thalhimer, Jr., at opening of the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike, June 30, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Thalhimer's Window #2, May 23, 1958 (Box 9)
    - Thalhimer's Window #2 - Crowds outside (I-II), May 19, 20, 23, 1958, 2 sleeves (Box 9)
    - Bill Thompson - WRVA - TV Hearing (I-III), 3 sleeves (Box 9)
    - Richard B. Tisdale - 1957 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 25, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Richard Tisdale - ALCOA "Care-free Home", Dec. 10, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Tobacco Festival (I-III), 3 sleeves (Box 9)
    - Tobacco Festival 1961 - Alden Aaroe, Joyce Cook, and Mike Garthright doing broadcasts, Sept. 30, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Tobacco Festival 1961 - Naming of Queen, Miss Sandra Leigh Baker, Danville, Virginia, Sept. 30, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Tobacco Festival 1961 - Shots from Press Box, Sept. 30, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Tobacco Festival 1961 - Crowd Shots, Sept. 30, 1961 (Box 9)
    - Tobacco Festival Opening Bell at The Arena - Tommy Dorsey Orchestra with Sam Donahue (singer Jeannie Thomas), Sept. 22, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Traffic Department - Bertha Hewlett and Malcolm Roddenberry (Box 9)
    - Trafficopter (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Building (WRVA Radio), Dec. 17, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Building (WRVA) - exterior (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Building at Varina (WRVA Radio), May 23-24, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter with Ted Chezik (WRVA Radio) - RCA 20 KW FM, Dec. 20, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Control Room Shots with Dubarry Crowder and Fred Hamilton, Dec. 17, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter - Dummy Antenna (WRVA Radio), Jan. 12, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter - Emergency Power Generator with Wilson Yarborough (WRVA-Radio), Jan. 12, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter with Leroy Foster and Fred Hamilton (WRVA-Radio) RCA 50 KW AM (I-II), Dec. 15, 1962, 2 sleeves (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Line Dryer (WRVA-Radio) - Hendricks, Dec. 20, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter (New) - WRVA AM and FM RCA photos, Dec. 1961 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Power Supply - WRVA Radio, Dec. 15, 1962 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Towers Aerial Views (WRVA Radio), May 9, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Transmitter Towers, Varina (WRVA Radio) (I-II), May 23-24, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Transmitters - Mechanicsville (Box 9)
    - Transmitters - Test Shots (WRVA Radio), Dec. 8, 1962 (Box 9)
    - TV Hearing (I-X), 10 sleeves (Box 9)
    - TV Tower - Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Co., Nov. 10, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Twin Trophies Presentation, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Tuck, William M. - Governor of Virginia (Box 9)
    - Universal Motors on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Aug. 30, 1957 (Box 9)
    - Unidentified (Box 9)
    - Ray Vaughan, Oct. 24, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Ray Vaughan at 1957 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 25, 1957 (Box 10)
    - VEPCO Weathergram on WRVA Theatre Marquee, July 25, 1957 (Box 10)
    - VEPCO Weathergram on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Apr. 2, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Vest, Donald (Box 10)
    - Vick's Lobby Display, Feb. 22, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Vick's Window Display, Feb. 22, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Village Shopping Center Fashion Show (1-2), Mar. 21, 1959, 2 sleeves (Box 10)
    - Village Shopping Center Window Contest, Dec. 13, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Robert Wood Vincent, Jr. - World's Largest New Year's Greeting Card Winners (located at W. Main St. and Shields Ave.), Jan. 4, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Apples - Safeway Stores, Oct. 1958 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Apples Window Display, Oct. 30, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Apples Window Display, Oct. 22, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Apples on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Oct. 22, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Apples on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Oct. 6, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Mrs. Virginia Conquest with Red Barber Sports Show Sign, Apr. 5, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962, Leanora Elizabeth Stoneman, Sept. 21, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962 - Leanora Elizabeth Stoneman gets trophy from Richard D. Chumney, commissioner of agriculture, at State Fair opening, Sept. 21, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962 - Leanora Elizabeth Stoneman opening 1962 state fair, Sept. 21, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962 - Leanora Elizabeth Stoneman with Miss State Fair 1962 and Mr. Paul Napier of New York, Sept. 25, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962 - Leanora Elizabeth Stoneman with tractor driving contest winner, Sept. 25, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962 - Leanora Elizabeth Stoneman in evening dress, Sept. 28, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen 1962 and Miss State Fair with Maj. General Edwin Booth, Sept. 25, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen Contest 1963, Sept. 14, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Virginia Farm Queen Judges 1962 (Mrs. F. Frank Carr, Charles Stelling, Alden Aaroe, Edwin O. Meyer, Dr. Paul Sanders, Mrs. O. Warren Long), Sept. 11, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Virginia State Fair (Box 10)
    - Virginia Weekly (Box 10)
    - Voice of Democracy Program (Box 10)
    - V.P.P.A. - Edward R. Murrow Trophy Awarded for Best TV Reel (Box 10)
    - Walton, Elizabeth (Box 10)
    - George Washington Statue in Capitol Square, Oct. 10, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Waverly Fabrics at Miller and Rhoads, Oct. 24, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Waverly Fabrics - Silk Trading Co., Oct. 17, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Waverly Fabrics - Thalhimer's 2nd floor, Sept. 21, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Webster, A.T. (Box 10)
    - Western Electric 50 KW Transmitter and Associate Equipment (WRVA Radio), Dec. 15, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Westinghouse Light Bulbs Window Display, Oct. 2, 1959 (Box 10)
    - White, Eleanor (Box 10)
    - Ed Whitehead - ID shot, Feb. 11, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Ed Whitehead Making TV spots, Oct. 23, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Whitehead News Conference - Studio B (Box 10)
    - Whitehorne, Leonard (Box 10)
    - Paul Whiteman with Charlie Murdock, May 16, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Whitman's Candy Lobby Display, Dec. 14, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Whitman's Candy Window Display, Dec. 17, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with "Casey the Cop", June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Temple Cook, Ed Stone, and Bob Sorka of Stone-Heffner-Cook, June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Marvin Heffner of Stone-Heffner-Cook, June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Broaddus Jones at La Vogue Store, June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Thomas Leake, Vice-President, and William Wright, Sales Manager, Universal Motor Co., June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Guy Mengulas, Stephen's Lobster House, June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Lon Savage and Charlie Mahon of United Press, June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Lee Wicker, "Miss Portable Radio", with Miss Patricia Worsham, Grady Wolfe, and Laverne Cole, Galeski Photo Center, June 23-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Sandy Wicker and Diane Franklin with WRVA-Radio Booth at "Jaycees Carnival in Miniature", Apr. 17, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Sandy Wicker at N.F. Jacobs Remote, Nov. 26, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Sandy Wicker and Becky Rogers in WRVA-Radio outfits at State Fair, Sept. 24, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Sandy Wicker and Gloria Wright - Moto-Mower Contest, June 10, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Wicker Sisters in costume in Mobile Studio for Thalhimer's Toy Parade, Nov. 22, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Wicker Sisters, Sandy and Lee, with Bill Rothenberg, "Tall Tales Contest" Winner, Aug. 5, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Wicker Sisters, Sandy and Lee, with WRVA microphone, Aug. 5, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Wilkinson, Holland R. (I-II), 2 sleeves (Box 10)
    - Williams, Mrs. Alton Mildred (Box 10)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Thomas G. Williams, Winners of "Night on the Town" Contest, May 29, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Willis, Bill (Box 10)
    - Willow Lawn Shopping Center Remote - Mexican Promotion, July 31, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson - 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson at beeper recorder, Apr. 30, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson, Frank Brooks, Dick Tisdale - "Esso Reporter", Jaycees Carnival Winter Garden, Hotel Richmond, Apr. 15, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson and Jack Clements - Crippled Children's Hospital, Dec. 30, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson, "Esso Reporter", at Jaycee's Carnival Winter Garden, Hotel Richmond, Apr. 15, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson - Head Shots, Mar. 12, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson makes a call from Mobile News Unit, May 1, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson at Newsroom Typewriter, May 1, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Frank Wilson in Thalhimer's Window with engineers, Ed Hines and Dick Tisdale, May 19-23, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Jim Wilson - Barn Dance, July 21, 1956 (Box 10)
    - John Wilson Making TV Spots, Oct. 23, 1963 (Box 10)